Jakub Aniszewski

Software Engineer

Hello! My name is Kuba Aniszewski. Based in Wroclaw, Poland -I am Software Engineer with 2+ years of experience (primarily in testing). Currently I work as a Software Engineer in Test. In my free time, I focus on side projects and enjoy furthering my expertise in web development technologies.



Work Experience

"... tietoevcy

Software Engineer in Test

Nov 2022 - Present

Project for Renesas Electronics focused on testing Bluetooth Low Energy SDK. Automation of tests cases with Robot Framework and

MOSIA

Software **Engineer** in Test

Jul 2021 - Oct 2022

Python Working Student

Jan 2020 - Jun 2021

Hands-on experience in 5G BTS software testing, specifically in the security domain. I utilized Python, Robot Framework, and Selenium for test automation and actively reported bugs using JIRA. Proficient in Linux, I played a key role in the CI/CD processes. Additionally, I maintained regression tests and spearheaded the development of a web application for the test team using Python, Django, React, and Docker.

Projects

LinkVerse July 2023



Streamer Spotlight June 2023



Personal Portfolio & Blog

August 2023



Ø Visit aniszewski.dev!

A SvelteKit-powered link-aggregation app that centralizes profiles and content in a single shareable link. Utilizes Firebase for real-time data and authentication. Features customizable profiles and a user-friendly interface.

Streamer-rating web app using NestJS, MongoDB, and TypeORM for backend, and React for frontend. Features include streamer bios, platform info, content descriptions, and a like/dislike system.

Astro static site featuring achievements, projects, and skills, with a blog section for industry insights. Tailwind CSS ensures intuitive design and user-friendly navigation.

Education

Master's Degree in Computer Science Wroclaw University of Technology 2021 - 2023

Bachelor's Degree in **Computer Science**

Wroclaw University of Technology 2017 - 2021

IT Technician

Opole Electrical Schools Complex 2013 - 2017

Skills

Python

TupeScript

React

Contact Info



+48 692 706 767



jakubaniszewski@pm.me



www.aniszewski.dev